india is changing the nation is
transforming into a digitally empowered
ecosystem
organizations now need a transparent
responsive and faster payment solution
that helps them with efficient con
utilization and hassle-free
reconciliation introducing icici bank
customized digital payments a one-stop
solution
to manage all your disbursement related
requirements
here's what we offer manage all your
pays
manage budget manage and track
projects make payments through various
online modes
dashboard and digital wall online
reports
expenditure filing multiple
authorization for approvals
and otp based secure transactions
we can provide any of the above options
based on your requirements
registration for icici bank digital
payments customized solution is very
simple
all you need is get in touch with your
relationship manager
and get started now you can process
almost all your disbursement
requirements in few simple steps
simply login to icici bank digital
payments website
using your id and password all modules
opted by you will be available navigate
to appropriate section
for example pay for vendor registration
project tracker to update milestones
payments to process just-in-time
payments
all activities are approval based as per
customized workflow
view consolidated dashboard and reports
or send an email to idgpt
icicibank.com